<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.3.4">Jekyll</generator><link href="https://davidkloepperwellness.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="https://davidkloepperwellness.com/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-10-25T01:47:28-06:00</updated><id>https://davidkloepperwellness.com/feed.xml</id><title type="html">DavidKloepperWellness</title><subtitle>Welcome to my Health and Fitness journey! I’m David Kloepper, dedicated to building both physical and mental strength. With goals like mastering the handstand pushup, running an ultra-marathon, and cultivating resilience, I’m committed to a lifestyle of balanced fitness. I follow the Solo Leveling workout daily—100 pushups, 100 sit-ups, 100 squats, and a 10K run—pushing my limits to complete it within an hour! Alongside training, I focus on healthy eating and quality sleep to fuel my progress. Join me as I explore new levels of health and fitness every day!</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Incredible Shredded Chicken Recipe for a High-Protein Diet</title><link href="https://davidkloepperwellness.com/recipe/2024/10/25/shredded-chicken-recipe.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Incredible Shredded Chicken Recipe for a High-Protein Diet" /><published>2024-10-25T01:09:50-06:00</published><updated>2024-10-25T01:09:50-06:00</updated><id>https://davidkloepperwellness.com/recipe/2024/10/25/shredded-chicken-recipe</id><content type="html" xml:base="https://davidkloepperwellness.com/recipe/2024/10/25/shredded-chicken-recipe.html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="amazing-shredded-chicken-recipe">Amazing Shredded Chicken Recipe</h1>

<p>If you’re looking for an easy, high-protein meal prep recipe, this shredded chicken is a game changer! Perfect for tacos, salads, wraps, or just on its own, this recipe makes juicy and flavorful chicken with minimal effort.</p>

<h2 id="ingredients">Ingredients</h2>
<ul>
  <li>1 1/2 lbs chicken breast</li>
  <li>4 cups water</li>
  <li>1 tsp salt</li>
  <li>1/3 tsp black pepper</li>
  <li>1/2 tsp garlic powder</li>
  <li>1 tsp onion powder</li>
  <li>2 tsp chili powder</li>
  <li>1 tsp dried oregano</li>
  <li>1/4 tsp ground cumin</li>
</ul>

<h2 id="instructions">Instructions</h2>
<ol>
  <li><strong>Prepare Ingredients</strong>: Rinse the chicken breasts and place them in a 2-quart pot. Add all other ingredients.</li>
  <li><strong>Boil</strong>: Bring the pot to a boil over high heat.</li>
  <li><strong>Simmer</strong>: Once boiling, allow it to continue at a rolling boil for about 10 minutes. Then reduce the heat to medium.</li>
  <li><strong>Shred</strong>: After 30 minutes, check if the chicken is tender enough to shred. Use two forks or tongs to gently pull it apart.</li>
  <li><strong>Finish Cooking</strong>: Continue cooking until most of the liquid has evaporated, leaving just a small amount of sauce to keep the chicken moist.</li>
</ol>

<hr />

<p>This recipe takes a bit of time to cook but requires minimal attention. Once it’s cooking, you only need to check on it a couple of times. Enjoy your flavorful, protein-packed shredded chicken!</p>

<p>Thank you for reading!</p>]]></content><author><name></name></author><category term="recipe" /><summary type="html"><![CDATA[Amazing Shredded Chicken Recipe]]></summary></entry></feed>